<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>surminus</title>
    <link>https://surminus.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on surminus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Code released under the Apache 2.0 license.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 13:27:53 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://surminus.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Terraform Structures and Layouts</title>
      <link>https://surminus.github.io/post/terraform-structures-and-layouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 13:27:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surminus.github.io/post/terraform-structures-and-layouts/</guid>
      <description>Having recently moved role, one of my first tasks is to try and combine a mixture of CloudFormation JSON and custom Ruby scripts using Fog into a single repository using Terraform.
The biggest challenge to me was what structure the code should take.
Hashicorp provide &amp;ldquo;best practices&amp;rdquo; but these do not provide any conclusion on the structure.
There is also Terragrunt, which provides tooling around an opinionated structure (Everything-is-a-Module).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Over Engineering a Text File</title>
      <link>https://surminus.github.io/post/over-engineering-a-text-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 11:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surminus.github.io/post/over-engineering-a-text-file/</guid>
      <description>In the ultimate exercise of procrastination, last week I decided I would like to have a to-do list that I could edit via command line to help reduce context switching and I would like this list to be in Github so I could sync between home and work devices. I also thought friends or colleages could raise PRs if they wanted me to do something (a feature no-one has yet taken advantage of, fortunately).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favourite Tools</title>
      <link>https://surminus.github.io/post/my-favourite-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 17:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surminus.github.io/post/my-favourite-tools/</guid>
      <description>The market is flooded with great tooling, so I wanted to list a few of my favourites that I&amp;rsquo;ve used in the past.
Vale Vale is a linting tool for documentation. Stick it in CI pipeline to check for markdown (or whatever flavour documentation you use), tweak your requirements with styles, and set it to fail on poor grammar.
asciinema asciinema live records your terminal session and then uploads somewhere providing you with a link to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Hugo for My Blog</title>
      <link>https://surminus.github.io/post/using-hugo-for-my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 14:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://surminus.github.io/post/using-hugo-for-my-blog/</guid>
      <description>I recently decided to update my blog. I had brielfy touched Hugo before and I have used it again.
It really is a wonderful tool for content.
After almost 4 years at GDS, I&amp;rsquo;m moving on to FutureLearn. This blog signals the start of this new chapter in my career.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>